<projects>
    <project>
        <img>img/projects/retrochat.png</img>
        <name>Retro Chat</name>
        <urlname>retrochat</urlname>
        <descshort>A really cool and simple retro chat site!</descshort>
        <desc>I made this as a cool little web Socket.IO chat client with a retro feel, since retro sites are cool. :3 I designed this after a few things: the Apple II, old CRTs, and IRC clients. It is a simple mix between an online chatroom and an IRC client, all with the styling of a retro CRT. I wanted this to look and feel fun and retro, and I think I achieved it! I'm also obviously VERY proud of it!</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/RetroChat</ghub>
        <site shown="yes">https://retrochat-5u83.onrender.com/</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/rpsai.png</img>
        <name>RPS AI</name>
        <urlname>rpsai</urlname>
        <descshort>A very simple Rock, Paper, Scissors AI vs AI written in Python</descshort>
        <desc>The code is super simple, since Rock Paper Scissors is basically just a comparison of numbers. Rock beats scissors, paper beats rock, and scissors beats paper. We can put this into a list:

            ["rock", "paper", "scissors"]
            
            Then index the list, where rock is 0, paper is 1, and scissors is 2. Then have each AI pick a random one and compare them to see if one is bigger than the other, and determine the winner!</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/Simple-RPS-AI</ghub>
        <site shown="no">https://yourfurrydeveloper.github.io/FlowAnim/</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/flow.png</img>
        <name>Flow</name>
        <urlname>flowanim</urlname>
        <descshort>A cool little web animator</descshort>
        <desc>Flow is a little animator that I made, and I'm pretty proud of it! It has the ability to add keyframes and other elements, and I'm gonna add exporting.</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/FlowAnim</ghub>
        <site shown="yes">https://yourfurrydeveloper.github.io/FlowAnim/</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/freevector.png</img>
        <name>FreeVector</name>
        <urlname>freevector</urlname>
        <descshort>A simple and free SVG program</descshort>
        <desc>FreeVector is a pretty simple SVG program, with features like stroke type, size, saving, and more! The way I made it was a little odd, beacuse I made it by detecting onmousemove on the actual svg element, and then generating a line.</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/FreeVector</ghub>
        <site shown="yes">https://freevector.puter.com/</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/discord.png</img>
        <name>Discord Login</name>
        <urlname>dsclogin</urlname>
        <descshort>A recreation of the Discord login page</descshort>
        <desc>I made this beacuse I was bored, and also just wanted to practice my knowledge of CSS.

lol</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/Discord-Login-CSS</ghub>
        <site shown="no">https://freevector.puter.com/</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/replwebz.png</img>
        <name>ReplWebz</name>
        <urlname>replwebz</urlname>
        <descshort>A mock Internet</descshort>
        <desc>I made this because I wanted my own little Internet to control and curate sites for. This obviously isn't by any means close to how the Internet works, since the way it works is it just serves static HTML files, but it's a cool example! :3</desc>
        <ghub shown="no">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/Discord-Login-CSS</ghub>
        <site shown="yes">https://replwebz.puter.com/</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/oreo.png</img>
        <name>Oreo Generator</name>
        <urlname>orereo</urlname>
        <descshort>Pretty self-explanatory lol</descshort>
        <desc>A couple of my friends and I were sitting together eating lunch, and we were talking about accents and how British people say things. This SOMEHOW spiraled into me saying "OREREREREREREO," which made my friend (@ImNotNotUseless on YT) tell me that I should make an Oreo generator, so I whipped it up in 10 minutes, and the rest is history!</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/OREREO</ghub>
        <site shown="yes">https://orereo.puter.com/</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/infinitelibrary.png</img>
        <name>The Infinite Library</name>
        <urlname>infinitelibrary</urlname>
        <descshort>An odd-feeling liminal space</descshort>
        <desc>I have recently kinda been obsessed with liminal spaces lately, so I decided to make The Infinite Library. I do still OBVIOUSLY know it's an already existing thing lol, but I'm VERY proud of this, because it is truly infinite. It generates a room every time you get close, but it is still a MASSIVE WIP.</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/Infinite-Library/</ghub>
        <site shown="yes">https://yourfurrydeveloper.github.io/Infinite-Library/</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/tubermash.png</img>
        <name>TuberMash</name>
        <urlname>tubermash</urlname>
        <descshort>Like FaceMash, but with YouTubers!</descshort>
        <desc>I LOVE The Social Network, so I decided to create FaceMash, but with YouTubers. TuberMash does not require any connection to YouTube API, since you run the Python script to get the channels and their PFPs! I'm SUPER proud of this, and it's pretty cool! :3</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/TuberMash</ghub>
        <site shown="yes">https://tubermash.puter.com</site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/ninjatimer.png</img>
        <name>McTech Ninja Timing System</name>
        <urlname>mtns</urlname>
        <descshort>A cool recreation of the ninja timing and leaderboard system I made just for fun in 2 days while at Worlds!</descshort>
        <desc>I was a bit too nervous to compete in any ninja comps this season, so I wasn't able to compete in Worlds. What started off as me just recreating the leaderboard part almost 1:1 because I was dissatisfied and angry that the run order weren't scrolling at the same time spiraled into me literally RECREATING the timing system that they use! I feel like this is my BIGGEST project YET, and I am SOOOO proud of it!!! :3</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/McTech-Ninja-Timing-System</ghub>
        <site shown="no"></site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/EasyToolbar.js.svg</img>
        <name>EasyToolbar.js</name>
        <urlname>etbjs</urlname>
        <descshort>A Javascript library for HTML editor webapps or whatever you want!</descshort>
        <desc>EasyToolbar.js is a Javascript library for HTML editor webapps like paint apps or something, or just for whatever! It allows you to easily create a customizable toolbar, saving you LOTS of time trying to make your own.</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/EasyToolbarJs</ghub>
        <site shown="no"></site>
    </project>

    <project>
        <img>img/projects/3d-png-renderer.png</img>
        <name>3D PNG Renderer</name>
        <urlname>3dpngr</urlname>
        <descshort>A really, really cool PNG/GIF/any image 3D renderer! </descshort>
        <desc>I've always had an idea nagging at the back of my head that I could very easily create a 3D image renderer where you can input an image and it'll layer it to make it 3D. I knew that images with transparent backgrounds would look REALLY cool and 3D! You can input ANY image in ANY format!</desc>
        <ghub shown="yes">https://github.com/YourFurryDeveloper/3D-PNG-Renderer</ghub>
        <site shown="yes">https://yourfurrydeveloper.github.io/3D-PNG-Renderer</site>
    </project>
</projects>
